(Penny:)What's up with Ichabod?
(Leonard:)Oh, he's trying to make a new friend.
(Penny:)Oh, really? Well, good for him.
Unless he makes one out of wood
like Geppetto...
(Leonard:)...I don't think it's gonna happen.
(Penny:)Well, how did you guys become friends?
There was a flyer on the bulletin board
at the university:
"Roommate wanted.
Whistlers need not apply."
(Penny:)And you moved in anyway?
(Leonard:)I assumed he was joking.
(Leonard:)You'd be surprised how many
particle physicists have a whimsical side.
What about Howard and Raj?
How did he become friends with them?
(Leonard:)I don't know. How do carbon atoms
form a benzene ring?
(Leonard:)Proximity and valence electrons.
(Penny:)Well, yeah, sure,
when you put it that way.
(Penny:)But it all worked out, right?
(Leonard:)I suppose.
(Leonard:)I do miss whistling though.
(Penny:)Oh, come on. Really?
(Sheldon:)First warning.
(Scene:)Penny.
(Sheldon:)Penny. Penny.